

# **PROFILE**

I'm a freshman with six months of UI/UX design experience, and I've worked at small businesses as well as applied concepts in academic projects.

While I work as a user interface/user experience (UI/UX) designer

My specialisation is creating scalable UI/UX designs.

I adore constructing stuff.

While solving difficult technical challenges may be enjoyable in and of itself.

# CONTACT

PHONE: 438-929-2883

WEBSITE:

Divpatel9182.github.io

EMAIL:

div.patel9182@gmail.com

# **HOBBIES**

Designing Sketching Templating Photography Crypto Modelling

# DIVYANG PATEL

# **UI/UX** Designer

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/divyang-patel-8163981aa/

GitHub: https://github.com/divpatel9182

## **EDUCATION**

John Abbott College, Montreal, QC, Canada 2021 – Pursuing

Full Stack Developer Course

FrankFinn Institute, Gujrat, India 2016 - 2017 Diploma in Aviation

Vallabh Budhi Polytechnic, Gujrat, India

Diploma in Computer Engineering

### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

# FreeLancer UI/UX Developer

2020-2021

2012 - 2015

- Managed usability testing for landing pages in preparation for Web site redesign. Defined testing parameters, prepared prototypes, recruited users, facilitated tests and reported results
- Produced wireframes, XHTML code and CSS that contributed to user-centered design (UCD) efforts for dozens of Web pages
- Helped improve information architecture of site by assisting with card sorting, affinity diagramming and search log analysis

# **SKILLS**

- Usability Engineering
- Usability Testing
- Information Architecture
- Interaction Design
- User Research & Persona Creation
- Web Site & Multimedia Design
- Web Site Strategy & Analytics
- Wireframe Production
- Cascading Style Sheets (CSS)
- HTML & XHTML
- Flash, Fireworks & InDesign